You are back with a video, Axis
Bank has set up a little change above, you can
see a rise, that is
more than 1% here and in this
video channel, here we are going to talk about
who is the next person you want in the city,
enthusiasm in equity theme, options chain,
so this will be the last of the video and if you are
on the channel, please subscribe
and click on the bell and select and judge
that the health of your opening,
see 7000, the closing of
200 46.75 paise, the
face today is love and here in
front of the exam point, such people make 000
to 1006, take away the right of
₹400 151, okay, they have more or they
can see that
from here it is within the conditions and here
I would like to say then here you will see that the
stock will go positive,
more than the moon and to measure the long term Eminem,
please take the shoulder now, then
Take it because after this the city will bring you
back within this range, let me talk about which range
I am talking about this Prince here,
okay and here if
we talk about short term
investors and things here, then see,
I will tell you right now, should you continue here,
wait a little, there is
no business here and this level is
not confirmed here yet, we will give you everything else
after some time,
but till then you have to wait here,
okay, I will come back to medium term
investors, right now you should see that inside this range, the
flaw in the accuracy here, here as much as
and not as much as here, right now and
take the register inside this because if you see, for
two consecutive days the stock closed below this and movie
Kolkata,
okay, it closed below that here
because the day it closed below that, the
next day on Sunday morning, after cutting the train, the
next day here, the next day after these 12 days, the
problem here is that one should go for eating
and before that there will be a significant
fall here, then  There will be a significant
decline here because once this level is reached, then the
alarm will automatically trigger even if the
market is not very bullish,
due to which the government has said that a huge
decline will be seen here,
so if you want to take this effect then
take it, you had
told them about these two that if I do this
then brother, there will be a
robbery in the super train, let's talk about what
we say here, like there is a fit
toe embrasure, then believe me, there is a
Prince Clock, otherwise, let's talk about that too here,
if it is news, then there is
news, now you can go and check it
and keep it with you, the
link is given in the description,
friends, the account will be opened for ₹50, for
which you will get the price of J7,
plus from our side you will get pre-
invested free of cost here,
let's change the option here,
we do not have any power for you, so
please wait or you can get it from someone
else then  Whatever
video we have uploaded today, I request you to
go and check the target of Saat Chakra Wipro here and I hope
that if you like it then like the
channel, otherwise subscribe to
Parikrama Simaria village, so till then
bye.